{"data":[{"question":"Wolfgang met Michaela _____ the way to work.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- We say  \"on the way\"","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"2"},{"question":"Susanne is ____ a meeting.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- In: used to name the book, document, film etc where something or someone appears","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"2"},{"question":"I had a meal _____ the train.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Use at with particular positions or places\n- Use in with a position or place, when something or someone is inside a larger thing such as a room\n- Use on with a position or place, when one thing is attached to or touching another\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"2"},{"question":"My children are _____ home.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- We often say \"at home: stay at home, be at home\"","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"2"},{"question":"This is the best cake _____ the world.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- Use at with particular positions or places\n- Use in with a position or place, when something or someone is inside a larger thing such as a room\n- Use on with a position or place, when one thing is attached to or touching another\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"2"},{"question":"I stayed in a nice hotel _____ London.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":"\n\nPrepositions of Place: at, in, on\n- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet, in a industry...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"2"},{"question":"There's somebody _____ the door.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"2","explain":"\n\nPrepositions of Place: at, in, on\n- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet, in a industry...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"2"},{"question":"There are lots of managers ____ my company.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet, in a industry...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"2"},{"question":"Can you put the report _____ my desk, please?","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet, in a industry...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"2"},{"question":"We're opening a new factory ____ Italy.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"2"}]}